Picture Collection LSC.0099.a
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Grace, Princess of Monaco, 1929-1982., 1 item (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Graham, Gladys (Murphy) -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Grand Canyon National Park -- Views. (folder 2 of 4), 68 items (Folder 26)
- Grand Canyon National Park -- Views. (folder 4 of 4) (Folder 2)
- Grand Canyon National Park. (folder 1 of 4), 32 items (Folder 25)
- Grand Junction, Colo. -- Views., 8 items (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Grand Lake, Colo. -- Views., 3 items (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Grand Teton National Park -- Views., 2 items (Folder 5)
- Grand, Albert -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Grand, Sarah, pseud. -- Portrait., 1 items (Folder 3)
- Granger, Percy., 5 items (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Grant, J.F. -- Portrait., 1 items (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Grant, Ulysses Simpson, Pres. U.S., 1822-1885., 8 items (Folder 9)
- Granville, George Levenson-Gower, 2 earl of, 1815-1891., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Grass Valley, Calif., 2 items (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Gray, Raymond., 2 items (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Grayson, Charles, 1905- -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Great Britain -- Views., 56 items (Folder 14)
- Great Salt Lake -- Views., 6 items (Folder 15)
- Greece., 20 items (Folder 16)
- Greeley, Colo. -- Views., 38 items (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Green Mountain Falls, Colo. -- Views., 3 items (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Green River, Wyo. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Green, Donald R., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Green, Evelyn Everett, 1856-1932., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Green, Lucy Bird (Semple)., 8 items (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Green, Will Semple, 1832-1905, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 21, Folder 23)
  ALSE SHELVED*
- Green, William Sample, 1832-1905. (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Green, William, 1870-1952., 1 item (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Gregg, Josiah, 1806-1850? -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Grieg, Edvard Hagerup, 1843-1907, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Grierson, Francis, 1848-1927, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Griffin, John Strother, 1816-1898, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 28)
- Griffith Observatory, Los Angeles -- Views., 9 items (Folder 30)
- Griffith, Griffith Jenkins, 1850-1919, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Grossmont, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Guam -- Views., 83 items (Folder 2)
- Guasti, Secundo, Jr., 2 items (Folder 3)
- Gudehus, Heinrich -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Guerra, de la, Family -- Portrait., 31 items (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Guiol, Frederico M. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Gunnison, Colo. -- Views., 11 items (Folder 7)
- Gunther, John, 1901-1970, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Gutenberg, Johann, 1397?-1468, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 9)
- Guthrie, Okla., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Gwin, William McKendree, 1805-1903., 3 items (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Gwyn, Nell, 1650-1687, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Gyro Compass -- Views., 6 items (Folder 13)
- Haas, Walter., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Hadley, A., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Hail, Charles Henry -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Haile Selassie I, Emperor of Ethiopia, 1891-1975, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Hale, George Ellery., 2 items (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Hall, Anna Maria (Fielding) 1800-1881., 7 items (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Halliburton, Richard, 1900-1939, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Hamilton, E.M., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Hamilton, Henry, d. 1918, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Hancock, John, 1737-1793, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Hancock, Johnston -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Hanna, Phil Townsend, 1896-, 2 items (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Harding, Florence Kling, 1860-1924, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Harding, Warren G., 20 items (Folder 27)
- Hardy, Thomas, 1840-1928., 4 items (Folder 28)
- Harraden, Beatrice, 1864-1936., 2 items (Folder 29)
- Harris, Nicholas Boilvin Homes & Haunts -- Views., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Harrison, Mary St, Leger (Kingsley), 1852-1931, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Hart, William Surrey, 1870-1946, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Harte, Bret, 1836-1902., 2 items (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Harvard Univesrsity -- Views., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Hastings, Lansford W., 1819-1870?, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Hastings, Serranus Clinton, 1814-1893., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Hatton, Joseph, 1841-1907, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Havana, Cuba -- Views. (Folder 1)
- Hawaiian Islands -- Views. (folder 1 of 2), 9 items (Folder 13)
- Hawaiian Islands -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Hawaiian Islands., 60 items (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Hawkins, Sir Anthony Hope, 1863-1933., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Hawthorne, Nathaniel., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809., 2 items (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Hayes, Alfred, 1911-1985, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Hayes, Benjamin., 2 items (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Hayes, Roland, 1888-1977, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Hayes, Rutherford Birchard, Pres. U.S., 1822-1893., 2 items (Folder 8)
- Haynes, John Randolph, 1853-1937., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Hays, Wade -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Hazard, George W., 1842-1914, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Heard, Gerald, 1889-1971, -- Portrait., 6 items (Folder 3)
- Heard, Gerald, 1889-1971., 9 items (Folder 12)
- Hearst, Millicent Veronica (Willson) -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Hearst, William Randolph, 1863-1951, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Heather Lake, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Hector, Mrs. Annie (French), 1825-1902., 4 items (Folder 16)
- Heidelberg, Ger., 4 items (Folder 17)
- Heifetz, Jascha, 1901-1987., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Heinrich, Max, 1853-1916., 3 items (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Hellman, Isaias W., -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Hemet Dam., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Hemet, Calif. -- Views., 7 items (Folder 21)
- Henderson, J.A., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Henderson, Leon, 1895-1986., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Hendersonm William H., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Henry E. Huntington library and art gallery, San Marino, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Folder 26)
- Heron, Herbert -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Herrick, Myron T., 1854-1929., 2 items (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Hershey, Lewis Blaine, 1893-1977., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Herve, Mons. 1825-1892, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Hesse, Hermann, 1877-1962., 2 items (Folder 31)
- Hibbert-Ware, Mary Clementina (Stewart)., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Highland., 2 items (Folder 33)
- Higuera Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Hill, Laurance Landreth, 1887-1932., 2 items (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Hobergs, Calif. -- Views., 32 items (Folder 36)
- Hodge, Frederick Webb, 1864-1956., 28 items (Folder 37)
- Hofmann, Josef., 5 items (Folder 38)
- Holborow Hotel (Santa Monica, Calif.), 4 items (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Holbrook, Ariz. -- Views., 2 items (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Hollenbeck, Mrs. Elizabeth (Hatsfeldt), 1827-1918, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 41)
- Hollister, Calif. -- Views., 14 items (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Hollister, William M., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Hollywood Studio Strike, 1945-1948, -- Views., 6 items (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Hollywood Studio Strike, 1945-1948, -- Views., 18 items (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Adobe - Campo de Cahuenga)., 2 items (Folder 1)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Churches)., 2 items (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Clubs)., 2 items (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Festivals)., 11 items (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Hollywood Bowl)., 11 items (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Hotels)., 8 items (Folder 6)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Lookout Mountain)., 3 items (Folder 7)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Residences - Paul de Longpre)., 4 items (Folder 9)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Residences)., 25 items (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Schools)., 4 items (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Streets - Hollywood Blvd.)., 18 items (Folder 11)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views (Transportation)., 2 items (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Hollywood, Calif. -- Views., 46 items (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Hollywood, California. (Folder 7)
- Holmes, Charles H., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Holmes, Oliver Wendell., 4 items (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Holtville, California., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Holyoke, Colo. -- Views, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Homer, Louise Dilworth (Beatty), 2 items (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Honolulu., 11 items (Folder 19)
- Hood River, Ore., 4 items (Folder 21)
- Hood Thomas, 1799-1845., 4 items (Folder 22)
- Hood, Mount -- Views., 5 items (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Hook, Theodore, Edward, 1788-1841, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Hoover Dam., 31 items (Folder 24)
- Hoover, Herbert Clark, pres. U.S., 1874-1964, -- Portrait., 28 items (Folder 25)
- Hoover, John Edgar, 1895-1972, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Hopkins, Ernest Martin, 1877-1964., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Horne, Frederick Joseph, 1880-1959., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Hornitos., 9 items (Folder 29)
- Horton, Mildred (McAfee), 1900-1994., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Hosie, Dorothea (Soothill) Lady, 1885-1959., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Hotels, taverns, etc., 5 items (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Houdini, Harry, 1874-1926., 2 items (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Houghton, Richard Mouckton Milnes, 1st baron, 1809-1885., 1 item (Folder 34)
- Houseworth, Thomas -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Housman, Alfred Edward, 1859-1936., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Houston, Samuel, 1793-1863., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Howard, Volney Erksine, 1809-1889, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Howells, William Dean., 2 items (Folder 38)
- Howitt, William, 1792-1879., 2 items (Folder 39)
- Hubbard, Elbert, 1856-1915., 1 item (Folder 1)
- Hudson, William Henry, 1841-1922, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Hughes, Charles Evans, 1862-1948., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Hughes, Edwin, 1884-, 1 item (Folder 4)
- Hughes, Rupert, 1872-1956, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Hughes, Samuel C., 1829-, 3 items (Folder 6)
- Hughes, Thomas, 1822-1896., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Hughes, William E., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Hugo, Victor Marie, 1802-1885, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 9)
- Humboldt, Alexandre, Feiherr von, 1769-1859., 4 items (Folder 10)
- Hunt, William Holman., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Huntington Beach, Calif., 2 items (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Huntington Botanical Gardens, 17 items (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Huntington Hartford Foundation, Santa Monica -- Views., 3 items (Folder 15)
- Huntington, Collis Potter, 1821-1900., 4 items (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Huntington, Henry Edwards, 1850-1927, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Hurley, N.M. -- Views., 21 items (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Hurst, Fanny, 1889-, 2 items (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Hussey, George Frederick, 1894-1983., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Huxley, Aldous Leonard, 1894-1963., 33 items (Folder 20)
- Hyde Ranch, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Ibsen, Hendrik, 1828-1906., 2 items (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Ickes, Harold Le Claire, 1874-1952., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Idaho -- Views., 5 items (Folder 24)
- Idaho -- Views. (folder 1 of 2) (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Idaho -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Idaho Falls, Ida. -- Views., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Idaho Springs, Colo. -- Views., 37 items (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Idyllwild, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Folder 27)
- Illinois -- Views., 3 items (Folder 28)
- Imperial Valley, Calif., 32 items (Folder 30)
- Imperial, Calif., 16 items (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Independence, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 25, Folder 31)
- India -- Views., 1 item (Folder 8)
- India -- Views., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Indians of North America -- California -- Antiquities., 10 items (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Indians of North America -- Northwest, Pacific., 3 items (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Indians of North America -- Southwest, New. (folder 1 of 2), 101 items (Box 25, Folder 34)
  FULL
- Indians of North America -- Southwest, New. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Indians of North America -- Views., 1 item (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Indians of North America -- Views. (folder 1 of 2), 115 items (Box 26, Folder 1)
  FULL; ALSO SHELVED*
- Indians of North America -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Indio, Calif. -- Views., 13 items (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Indonesia -- Views. (folder 1 of 2) (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Indonesia -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Ingalls, John James, 1833-1900, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Ingelow, Jean, 1820-1897., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Inglewood, Calif., 2 items (Folder 7)
- Insley, George, Marshal of Santa Ana, Calif. in 1891., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Interior Decorations -- Views., 15 items (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Ireland -- Views., 4 items (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Isherwood, Christopher, 1904-1986., 3 items (Folder 11)
- Isleta, N.M., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Israel -- Views., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Israel -- Views., 16 items (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Italy. (folder 1 of 2), 61 items (Folder 14)
- Italy. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Jackson, Andrew, pres. U.S., 1767-1845., 2 items (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Jackson, Calif., 5 items (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Jackson, Grant, 1869-1925., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Jackson, Helen Maria (Fiske) Hunt, 1831-1885., 4 items (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Jackson, Robert Houghwout, 1892-1954., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Jackson, Thomas Johnathon, 1824-1863, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Jacob, Max, 1876-1944., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Jacobs, William Wymark, 1863-1943., 5 items (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Jacumba, Calif. -- Views., 25 items (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Jaggar, Thomas Augustus, 1871-1953., 1 item (Folder 11)
- James, George Wharton, 1858-1923., 5 items (Folder 12)
- James, Mrs. Florence Alice (Price) -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Jamul, Calif., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Japan -- Views., 3 items (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Japan -- Views., 46 items (Folder 15)
- Japanese in California -- Views., 6 items (Folder 16)
- Jaull, Alfred., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Java (Indonesia) -- Views., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Jay, Benjamin David., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Jefferies, James J., 1875-1953, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Jeffers, Robinson, 1887-1962, -- Portrait., 9 items (Folder 20)
- Jeffers, William Martin, 1876-1953., 1 item (Folder 21)
- Jefferson, Thomas, Pres. U.S., 1743-1826., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Jemez Springs, N.M. -- Views., 2 items (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Jenkins, Charles M., 1838- -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 25)
- Jerome, Jerome K., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Jerome, William Travers, 1859-1934., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Jerrold, Douglas William, 1803-1857., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Jewsbury, Geraldine Endsor, 1812-1880, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Joachim, Joseph -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 30)
- Johannesburg, California., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Johnson Canyon, Ariz., 3 items (Folder 32)
- Johnson Carlos, Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Johnson, Andrew, pres. U.S., 1808-1875, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Johnson, Hiram Warren, 1866-1945, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Johnson, Hiram Warren, 1866-1945, -- Portrait., 5 items (Folder 35)
- Johnson, Mordecai Wyatt, 1890- -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Johnson, Noble Mark, 1881-1978., 2 items (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Johnston, Eric Allen, 1896-1963, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Jolon, Monterey Co., California, 1 item (Folder 39)
- Jones, Edward Wadsworh, 1840-1934., 1 item (Folder 40)
- Jones, Jessie Holman, 1874-1945., 1 item (Folder 41)
- Jones, John Paul, 1747-1792, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 42)
- Jones, Rev. Samuel Porter, 1847-1906, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Jordan, David Starr., 2 items (Folder 44)
- Joughin, Mrs. Andrew., 1 item (Folder 45)
- Journet, Marcel, 1867-1962, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 46)
- Joyce, James, 1882-1941, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Juvenile Delinquency - California - Los Angeles -- Views., 6 items (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Kaalback., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Kansas -- Views., 53 items (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Kearney, Denis, 1847-1907, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Kearny, Stephen Watts, 1794-1848, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Keats, John., 4 items (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Keller Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 6)
- Kelley, John -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Kemble, Edward Windsor, 1861-1933., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Kennedy, Jacqueline Lee (Bourvier), 1929-1994, -- Portrait. (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Kennedy, John Fitzgerald, pres. of U.S., 1917-1963., 3 items (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Kent, Rockwell, 1882-1971, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Kern County, Calif., 4 items (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Kern River, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Killgore, Gabriel M., 1825-1863., 4 items (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Kimberly, Nev. -- Views., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 14)
- King, Andrew Jackson., 1 item (Folder 15)
- King, Martin Luther, 1929-1968, -- Portrait., 10 items (Folder 16)
- Kinglake, Alexander William., 1 item (Folder 17)
- Kings Canyon National Park, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Kings Canyon National Park., 2 items (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Kingsley, Charles, 1819-1875., 6 items (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Kipling, Rudyard, 1865-1936, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Kirk, Norman Thomas, 1888-1960., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Kitchen, Pete., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Kitchens -- Views., 5 items (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Knight, Goodwin Jess, 1896-1970., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Knights Ferry, Calif., 2 items (Folder 25)
- Knowland, William Fife, 1908-1974, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Knox, Franklin, 1874-1944., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Kocian -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Kokoweef, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 29)
- Komroff, Manuel, 1890-1974., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Kooksia, Ida. -- Views., 7 items (Folder 32)
- Kool, P.J., 2 items (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Krausse -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Kreisler, Fritz., 2 items (Folder 34)
- La Grande, Ore. -- Views., 5 items (Folder 35)
- La Honda, Calif., 1 item (Folder 37)
- La Jolla, 44 items (Box 28, Folder 44)
- La Junta, Colo. -- Views., 33 items (Box 29, Folder 1)
- La Mirada, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 4)
- La Quinta, Calif. -- Views., 21 items (Folder 14)
- La Viata, Manuelita, 1787-1902, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 22)
- Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Ives Roch Gilbert de Motier, marquis de, 1757-1834, -- Portrait. (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Laguna Beach., 33 items (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Lake Chelan, Washington -- Views., 2 items (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Lake County, California -- Views/, 1 item (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Lakeport, Calif. -- Views., 38 items (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Lakes., 2 items (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Lakeside, Calif., 14 items (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Lakewood, Colo. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 43)
- Lamar, Colo. -- Views., 10 items (Folder 2)
- Lamartine, Alphonse Marie Louis De, 1790-1869., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Lamy, N.M. -- Views., 2 items (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Lancaster, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Lancey, Thomas Crosby, 1824-1885., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Land, Emory Scott, 1879-1971, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Landis, James McCauley, 1899-1964., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Landon, Letitia Elizabeth, 1802-1838., 1 item (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Lanfranco, John T., 1 item (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Langmuir, Irving, 1881-1957., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Lankershim, Isaac, 1 item (Folder 13)
- Laramie, Wyo. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Lardner, Ring Wilmer, 1885-1933., 1 item (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Las Cruces, N.M. -- Views., 69 items (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Las Vegas, Nev. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 20)
- Las Vegas, New Mexico., 54 items (Folder 21)
- Lassangue, Madame E., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Lassen Volcanic National Park, Calif. -- Views., 5 items (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Lawrence, David Herbert, 1885-1930, -- Portrait., 16 items (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Lawrence, David, 1888-, 1 item (Folder 23)
- Layne, Joseph Gregg., 53 items (Folder 25)
- Lead Industry and Trade -- Views., 17 items (Folder 26)
- Leadville, Colo. -- Views., 68 items (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Lean, Florence (Marryat) Church, 1837-1899., 2 items (Box 29, Folder 28)
- LeConte, Joseph, 1823-1901., 2 items (Folder 29)
- Lecouvreur, Theodor Maxilimian Ferdinand Franz, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Lee, Joshua Bryan, 1892-1967., 1 item (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Lee, Robert Edward, 1807-1870, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Leech, John, 1817-1864, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Lehman, Herbert Henry, 1878-1963., 1 item (Folder 34)
- Leicester, England., 91 items (Folder 35)
- Leighton, Clare Veronica Hope, 1900- -- Portrait., 4 items (Folder 1)
- Leighton, Frederic, Baron, 1830-1896., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Leimert Park (Los Angeles, Calif.), 9 items (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Leningrad., 13 items (Folder 4)
- Leonardo Da Vinci, 1452-1519, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Leslie, Kenneth, 1892-, 2 items (Folder 6)
- Lessing, Gotthold Ephraim, 1729-1781, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Levinson, Harry A. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Lewis, E.L. -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 9)
- Lewis, John Frederick., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Lewis, Mrs. Mark B. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Lhevinne, Josef, 1874-1944., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Libraries -- Views., 3 items (Folder 14)
- Life-Boats -- Views., 2 items (Folder 15)
- Life-Saving Apparatus -- Views., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Liggett, Hunter, 1857-1935., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Limoneria Ranch, Santa Paula, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Lincoln, Abraham, pres. U.S., 1809-1865. (Folder 19)
  ALSO* and SHELVED IN BOX OVER FILE CABINENT
- Lincoln, New Mexico., 5 items (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Lincoln, Robert Todd, 1843-1926., 2 items (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Lippincott, Joseph Barlow, 1864-1942., 4 items (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Lipsky, Louis, 1876-1963, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 24)
- Littlefield, John C., 2 items (Folder 25)
- Litzenberger, Carl., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Livermore, Calif. -- Views., 17 items (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Llano, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Lloyd, Thomas., 1 item (Folder 29)
- Lodi, Calif. -- Views., 23 items (Folder 30)
- Logan, Utah -- Views., 11 items (Folder 31)
- Lokoya, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Loma Linda, Calif. -- Views., 12 items (Box 30, Folder 33)
- London, Jack, 1876-1916., 11 items (Folder 35)
- London., 27 items (Folder 34)
- Lone Pine, Calif., 3 items (Folder 36)
- Long Beach -- Views. (folder 1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 37)
  *ALSO SHELVED
- Long Beach -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Folder 38)
- Long Beach, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Long, Breckinridge, 1881-1958., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Longmont, Colo. -- Views., 20 items (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Lookout Mountain, Tenn., 1 item (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Lopez Family -- Portrait., 10 items (Box 30, Folder 42)
- Lopez Station., 1 item (Folder 43)
- Lordsburg, N.M. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 44)
- Loretto Heights College, Loretto, Colo. -- Views., 12 items (Folder 45)
- Los Angeles -- Views (Buildings). (folder 1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles -- Views (Buildings). (folder 2 of 2) (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles -- Views (Freeways). (Folder 2)
- Los Angeles -- Views (Harbors). (folder 1 of 2) (Folder 4)
- Los Angeles -- Views (Harbors). (folder 2 of 2) (Folder 5)
- Los Angeles -- Views (Residences). (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles -- Views (Streets - Mulholland Drive). (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Board of Education -- Portrait. (Folder 3)
- Los Angeles Booksellers -- Portraits., 67 items (Folder 1)